# **SAJJAD ALI**

Peshwar Pakistan +923119942281 https://github.com/asajjad308 https://www.linkedin.com/in/sajj ad-ali-658898105/ asajjad308@gmail.com

#### **PROFILE**

Dedicated and experienced computer engineer with Extensive knowledge Of engineering principles, theories, specifications, And Standards, Bringing leadership, drive, and over 4+ years of experience Appreciable Track record of finishing projects within budget and in time

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Syncode Ltd,** cyprus — software developer (remote)

Sep 2022-PRESENT (PART TIME)

Full stack developer providing support in Asp.net , Mysql db, MongoDb, node js ,express js, SpringBoot,Reactjs,Django,FastApi

# **MathLogic/ Mintra,** cyprus — software developer ()

Sep 2020 - 2024

Full stack developer providing support in Asp.net , Mysql db, MongoDb, node js ,express js, SpringBoot,Reactjs,Django,FastApi

### **Kaner Group of companies**, Cyprus — software developer

July 2018 - Aug 2020

Full stack developer providing support in Asp.net , Mysql db, node js , Flutter , web services , Rest Api .Django,FastApi

### **Pnp computers**, Cyprus — Software developer

Feb 2017- Mar 2018

Software developer providing support in Asp.net, Mysql db.

# **Oral Guvenlik and Security systems,** Cyprus — *Software Engineer*

Jan 2016- Jan 2017

Providing services in Router and switches configuration plus server management, camera and security systems installation .

#### SKILLS/STACK

Team Player, Analytical thinker, problem solver, Excellent Mathematical Skills, Project Management, switches and routers configuration, Software dev,AI,Data Science Docker,MERN,MEAN

### Accreditation

**ABET** 

#### Licenses

PEC(pakistan engineering council)

# Version Control & Project Management

Gitlab

Github

Iira

Azure portal, aws

#### OS

Linux, windows, Mac

#### **Programing Languages**

C#,Java,C,C++,Dart,Php,Python Javascript,Liquid,Jinja Kotlin ,twig,R,typescript

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Eastern Mediterranean University,** Cyprus — Bs Computer Engineering

Mar 2014 - Jan 2018

#### **DataBase**

Mysql ,Mongodb,MariaDB, Postgre

#### **Frameworks**

**PROJECTS** Django

Asp.net

CAR WASHING APP
Asp.net Core/Maui

https://alvisbilvard.se/ Xamarin
https://bokatid.biltvattnu.se/ FastAPI

https://login.biltvattnu.se/ Wordpress

Express js

PROFESSIONAL FINDING APP
SpringBoot

https://joomastoras.com/

Reactjs

Nextjs

Sophia school LMS Angular <a href="https://schools.mysophia.eu/">https://schools.mysophia.eu/</a>

**ECOMMERCE** Codeigniter

https://edvardson.se/

Laravel

TRAININGpORTAL

https://www.trainingportal.co.uk/mintra/p/scis

https://www..mintra.no/admin-ui/ frontend project

InvoiceApi for mintra(express js)

**Mycert/Mycert web Api** — certificate issuing system mainly focused on maritime industry

This App is the gateway between maritime organizations, seafarers and maritime schools

https://www.mycert.com/

**LANGUAGES** 

Craft cms

English,Urdu

# Kaner Portal/Kaner Web Services and AP-

# Employee/product management system

This project is helping kaner group to manage their employees and their products (i have developed employee scanner app during covid19 the purpose of this app was to track and keep employee information using qrcode)